约翰逊夫人 您是怎么找到我的呢
Mrs. Johnson, may I ask how you found me?
我的朋友玛格丽特・吉布森告诉我的
I was given your name through my friend Margaret Gibson.
我们曾一起拍过电影
She and I used to be in pictures together.
她说你帮她解决了
She said you were able to help her
一些问题
with her... problem.
玛格丽特 我记得
Margaret, yes.
她是个可爱的女孩
She's a lovely girl.
你看 我已经结婚了
I'm married, you see.
丈夫并不知道我期望着
My husband doesn't even know that I'm expecting...
约翰逊夫人 你不必多加解释
Mrs. Johnson, you don't need to explain anything to me.
我是来帮助你的
I'm here to help you.
那么 有多久身孕呢
So, how far along are you?
三个星期
Three weeks.
请进
Please.
穿过去就是
Just through there.
医生 这支温度计
Doctor, there must be something wrong
肯定有问题
with this thermometer.
上面显示体温75度[约等于24摄氏度]
It says her body temperature is 75 degrees.
这可能吗
Can that be right?
别傻了
Don't be a fool.
这不可能
She'd be dead.
好了 亲爱的 我要你吸气
All right, my dear, I want you to breathe in
然后倒数
and count backwards.
就这样
There you are.
嘘
Shh...
很好
Very good.
嘘
Shh...
好了
There you are.
给我大手术刀
Get me the big knife.
准备好医用盘
Ready the pan.
准备缝合
Closing her up.
护士 丢掉它
Nurse, dispose of that.
我觉得它还活着
I think it's still alive.
恭喜你 是个男孩
Congratulations, it's a boy.
嗨 爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
霍尔登
Holden?
Holden!
噢
Oh.
为什么和你做爱这么爽
Why is it so good with you?
因为你是孤儿
Because you're an orphan.
孤儿喜欢我这样的女孩
Orphans love girls like me
感觉就像是爸妈都在身边
because it's like Mommy and Daddy are both in the room.
全身心爱着你
Loving you to pieces.
我有东西给你
I got you something.
帮助你开始
Just to get you started.
最基础的 勃朗特和王尔德的作品
The basics-- Bronte and Wilde.
你会爱上王尔德的
Oh, you're gonna love Wilde.
哇
Wow.
谢谢 莉兹
Thanks, Liz.
我有好多年没有正经读过书了
I don't think I've read anything in years
大部分时间看的
that didn't have the month and a picture
都是一些关于明星娱乐的杂志
of Jennifer Aniston or Kim K. On the cover.
我搬来这之后才开始阅读名著
I never did any real reading till I moved out here.
很大原因是前台工作很空闲
Part of it was all the free time at the desk,
但我觉得如果要让自己全身心放下时
but I also think you can't shut down one part of yourself
不能只是一部分
without shutting down the whole thing.
当我将本我暴露出来时
And when I let the Liz out,
我可以看见和感受
I could see and feel
体验世界
and... taste.
甚至去爱
And love.
你爱我吗
Do you love me?
哦
Oh...
我不知道
I don't know.
我想是吧
I think so,
但是 该死的 你这么帅让人怎么办
but, goddamn it, who can tell when you're so damn handsome?
我想我爱你
I think I love you.
-别戏弄我  -我认真的
- Don't tease me. - I'm serious.
当我到大厅见你时
When I come down to the lobby and see you,
你看到我 似乎真的很开心
it's like... you're genuinely happy to see me.
我相信你
I believe you.
当你出现时
When you come down,
对我来说
it's like...
就好像圣诞节清晨那样欣喜
it's like it's Christmas morning for me.
我想说 从没有人对我有过这种想法
I mean, no one's ever felt that way about me before.
从来没有
Ever.
甚至人们觉得
No one's even thought I was smart enough
我看不懂书
to give real books to.
你知道最奇怪的是什么吗
And you want to know the weirdest part?
当我们做爱时 我发誓
When we screw, I swear,
这是我这辈子最硬的时候
I've never come harder in my life.
太奇怪了
It's so bizarre.
我并不是同性恋
Uh, I'm not gay or anything.
喜欢我不代表你是同性恋
You're not gay for being with me.
我是女孩
I'm a girl.
我喜欢男人
I'm a hetero girl.
谢谢你 将我看做女孩
Thank you... for seeing the girl.
喂
Hey.
你为什么哭了
Why are you crying?
因为我爱你
Because I do love you.
但我们不会有什么结果的
And I know this doesn't end well.
这也不该发生
And it shouldn't.
特别是我对女伯爵做了那些事后
Not after what I've done to The Countess.
她把一切给了我
She gave me everything.
我们这也对她是错误的
It's wrong what we're doing to her.
喂
Hey.
爱情怎么会是错误的呢
How can love be wrong?
如果她看到我们在一起
If she could just see us together,
她会理解的
she'd understand.
你想体验新花样吗
Do you want me to do something different?
和女人在一起都会这样
This always to me with women.
我爱她们
I love them.
我爱她们的身体
I love their bodies and...
还有她们的柔情
...and their femininity
还有性爱
and their sex...
但我的上下两部分是分开运转的
but my cock and my mind operate separately.
我很尴尬
I'm very embarrassed.
不尴尬
Hardly embarrassing.
这不是危机
This isn't a crisis.
这是一次
It's a...
邀你去探险的机会
invitation for an adventure.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我得走了
I got to go.
不要
Don't...
不要和她说起我们 还不能说 好吗
don't talk to her about us... just yet, okay?
让这段感情 暂时成为我们的秘密
Let it be just ours... for a little while longer.
什么情况
What's this?
我和德雷克先生需要帮助
I need some help with Mr. Drake.
我不是同性恋
I'm not gay.
瞎说
Bullshit.
几周前 你在我办公室
A few weeks ago, you were in my office
和我说起你在狱中上过的男人们
telling me about all the dick you took in prison.
老兄 我和你开玩笑呢
I was messing with you, man.
监狱的事情都是瞎编的
I made up all that jail stuff.
我有自己的理由
I had my reasons.
你只要把他弄硬 宝贝
Just fluff him up for me a bit, baby.
之后的事我来做
I'll finish him off.
我不想做
I don't want to.
没兴致
I'm not into it.
你有一小时的时间
You are for the next hour.
我需要你帮助
I need your help.
在我用西洋棋之夜来欢迎你
Judging by how fast you put your nose up in the air
而你不假思索地拒绝我时
when I offered you an evening of backgammon and ros--
我可以很明确地告诉你 我不是你的好闺蜜
to welcome you, no less-- I'm really not your girl.
约翰发现了睡棺
John somehow discovered the sleeping chamber.
他现在哪
Where is he now?
我给他用了两毫克咪达唑仑
I gave him two milligrams of Versed
现在正处于睡眠状态
to keep him out for a couple of hours.
他不能知道我和霍尔登的事
He can't know about Holden and me.
失去他时我简直活不下去
I almost died when I lost him.